

CONTACT

3

+639165990579



Lapu-lapu City, Cebu



jamesdaniel288@gmail.com



jdenovero.com

SKILLS

Front-End & Back-End Development

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP, and MySQL

WordPress Development

Divi, Elementor, Beaver, and Webflow

jQuery, Ajax and Vue.js

Logical Approach

Creative Ability

EDUCATION

Ernesto Rondon High School

2010 - 2014

146 Rd 3, Project 6, Quezon City, Metro Manila

University of Cebu Lapu Lapu and Mandaue

2014 - 2018

A. C. Cortes Ave, Mandaue City, Cebu

JAMES DANIEL ENOVERO

Web Developer

ABOUT ME

I'm a web developer with over 6 years of experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP. I also have expertise in Vue.js for developing web and mobile applications. I'm continuously learning and adapting to the latest industry trends.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Proweaver, Inc.

August 2018 - April 2022

Converting design layouts into website pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and WordPress, maintaining and improving existing websites, interpreting and implementing instructions from clients, collaborating with team members, and fixing any website issues or bugs.

Lead Web Developer

Proweaver. Inc.

April 2022 - January 2023

Mentoring and providing guidance to newbie developers. Reviewing code written by other developers. Staying up-to-date with new technologies and tools that could improve the development process.

Web Programmer

Proweaver, Inc.

January 2023 - October 2023

Developing web and mobile applications using Vue.js. Creating and improving office tools. Conducting code reviews and providing feedback to other developers to ensure code quality and maintainability.